iSpring fans welcome to another
iSpring粉丝欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装弹簧提示
installment we're gonna take a look at
分期付款，我们来看看
something that for the moment just for
暂时只为
the moment doesn't have all that much to
当下没有那么多
do with spring but I think is
与春天有关，但我认为是
particularly interesting in light of
鉴于
where things are going with spring and
春天到哪里去了，
what the opportunities are for this
这有什么机会
particular technology namely we're gonna
特殊的技术，我们将
look at our socket now our socket is a
看看我们的插座，现在我们的插座是
sort of a we could spend all day we
我们可以整天度过的
really could we could spend all day just
真的可以花一整天
talking but our socket but briefly our
说话，但我们的插座，但简短地我们
socket is a protocol that was developed
套接字是已开发的协议
at Facebook it is the result of a use
在Facebook上，这是使用的结果
case of a need at Facebook to be able to
在Facebook需要能够
describe intubation between systems in a
描述一个系统之间的插管
platform and language agnostic way it is
平台和语言不可知的方式
a a protocol that is as I say runtime
一个协议，正如我所说的运行时
and plastun platform agnostic it doesn't
和plastun平台无关的
matter if you're running it on Java
在Java上运行是否重要
or.net or whatever there are multiple
or.net或其他多个
ways to consume it
消费方式
it is a protocol that is modeled after
这是一个模仿的协议
the sort of the use cases of large scale
大型用例的种类
services and and as such it follows that
服务，因此
it integrates natively the reactive
它本地集成了反应式
streams concepts at the protocol layer
在协议层流式传输概念
at the protocol level is actually a
在协议级别上实际上是
protocol that supports reactive stream
支持反应流的协议
concepts and the the Facebook in
概念和Facebook中的
implementations are of which there are
其中的实现
three
三
right now there's one for C++ one for
现在有一个C ++
JavaScript and one for Java the Java
JavaScript和Java的Java
based implementation naturally builds
基于自然的实现
upon reactor and so reactor of courses
在反应堆等课程上
are the spring teams sort of reactive
春季队反应如何
library for for intubation that implants
用于植入的插管库
and supports the reactive stream
并支持反应流
specification and the question then of
规格和问题
course is why are socket right why why
当然是为什么插座正确，为什么，为什么
why this solution to what might seem and
为什么这种解决方案可能看起来像
already crowded space well when you
当你已经挤满了空间
consider what we're trying to do here
考虑我们在这里想要做什么
we're trying to integrate different
我们正在尝试整合不同的
different despaired of disparate sort of
绝望的不同
services and systems and so on
服务和系统等
reactive streams I think we can all
反应性流，我想我们都可以
agree it provides a nice foundation
同意它提供了良好的基础
from modeling that integration in Java
用Java建模集成
right relax
放松
reactive streams rely upon asynchronous
反应流依赖异步
message passing to establish boundaries
消息传递以建立边界
between components and ensure loose
组件之间并确保松动
complic coupling there are other
复杂的耦合还有其他
benefits right there's location
好处就在这里
transparency there's isolation etc and
透明有隔离等，并且
there's also a you know in true
还有一个你真正知道的
functional style there's a a first-class
功能风格有一流的
way of expressing errors as in the same
表示错误的方式
way that you treat and manage data you
处理和管理数据的方式
manage and treat errors because you have
管理和处理错误，因为您有
message passing you have asynchronous
消息传递您有异步
sort of decoupling between integration
集成之间的某种解耦
boundaries you can you can very easily
您可以轻松地划分界限
now apply messaging sort of patterns to
现在将消息传递模式应用于
reactive code right you can use things
可以使用反应式代码的东西
like load balancing you can you can
像负载平衡一样，您可以
scale out horizontally you can do
横向扩展就可以了
pub/sub you can do you can do flow
pub / sub，你可以做，你可以做
control by pushing back on the producer
通过推回生产者进行控制
of the messages so you have a lot of
的消息，所以你有很多
really interesting ideas in the reactive
反应堆中非常有趣的想法
stream specification and these are the
流规范，这些是
things that you want in a sort of
你想要的东西
application layer protocol now some
应用层协议现在有些
might look at HTTP too and say well
可能也会看HTTP并说得好
isn't that an application layer protocol
那不是应用层协议
and the answer is no really it's not
答案是不，不是
it's a it's a much better HTTP HTTP to
这是一个更好的HTTP HTTP
is a more efficient HTTP but ultimately
是更有效的HTTP，但最终
HTTP olicity that was designed for
专为以下目的设计的HTTP策略
document retrieval the verbs expressed
文档检索所表达的动词
there in map to document retrieval this
在地图上有文档检索此
is not a application layer protocol it
不是应用层协议
doesn't really support anything besides
真的不支持什么
request response there is the concept of
要求回应有概念
of push promises right this idea that
的推销承诺会纠正这个想法，
you can send down preemptively
您可以抢先寄出
information down to the client but that
信息传给客户，但那
still requires an explicit request it's
仍然需要一个明确的请求
not true bi-directional communication
不是真正的双向通讯
and if you want to do things like
如果你想做类似的事情
fire-and-forget you can't do that right
一劳永逸，你做不到
it's not as easy because you you have
这不是那么容易，因为你有
you the the machinery of the web server
您是Web服务器的机器
is still going to process the response
仍将处理响应
even if the client then ignores it right
即使客户随后无视它
so you run into problems and use HTTP
所以您遇到问题并使用HTTP
for application level concerns the the
对于应用程序级别而言，
our socket website explains some of
我们的套接字网站解释了一些
these but basically there are some
这些，但基本上有一些
issues there are some issues that that
有一些问题
bubble up from trying to use HTTP in
从尝试使用HTTP冒泡
this way one is that when you do HTTP 1
这样一来，当您执行HTTP 1时
dot X you get a lot you know head of
点X，您会知道很多
line blocking we're effectively the only
行阻塞，我们实际上是唯一的
one requests can can be outstanding on a
一个请求可以在一个
connection at a time this is not a
一次连接不是
tenable situation to be and when you
以及当你时的局面
have large scale and you need to be able
有大规模，你需要能够
to queue and then process a bunch of
排队，然后处理一堆
work as possible it should be a 1.1
工作尽可能是1.1
tried to fix this with pipelining but of
试图用流水线解决这个问题，但
course it it didn't completely address
当然，它并没有完全解决
the problem large or slow response can
问题大或反应慢会
still block others behind it and
仍然阻止其他人
pipelining is hard to team them
流水线很难团队合作
incorrectly because you've got lots of
错误地，因为你有很多
middle middle ware in there in the
中间的中间件
pipeline a lot of a middleware in in
在管道中传输许多中间件
between different producers and
在不同的生产者之间
consumers that don't necessarily know
不一定知道的消费者
what you're trying to do so they can
您正在尝试做什么，以便他们可以
they can end up trying to proxy for
他们最终可能会尝试代理
example incorrectly and so on so so we
例子不正确等等，所以我们
then see that a there's a number of
然后看到有很多
heuristics that people rely upon
人们所依赖的启发式
obviously multiplexing fixes some of
显然，多路复用修复了
this it allows you to have multiple
这可以让你拥有多个
requests in-flight at the same time but
同时请求飞行中，但
we still don't have everything we need
我们仍然没有我们需要的一切
right we still don't have everything you
是的，我们还没有您拥有的一切
need and ultimately we we need support
需要，最终我们需要支持
for things like persistent connections
用于持久连接
right so so persistent connections help
是的，所以持久连接有助于
you reduce the number of open
您减少开门次数
connections at a time right obviously
一次正确的连接
too many open connections is a bad thing
太多的开放连接是一件坏事
because it means that your network
因为这意味着您的网络
infrastructure is now trying to deal
基础设施现在正试图应对
with congestion and the congestion can
与拥挤，拥挤可以
punish otherwise well-behaved
惩罚本来乖巧的人
applications who are running in the same
在同一环境中运行的应用程序
area in the same space so you're
在同一空间中的区域，因此您
stealing a system essentially from other
实质上是从其他地方窃取系统
better-behaved applications so that's
表现更好的应用程序
that these are all problematic issues
这些都是有问题的问题
with HTTP there's also the other issue
与HTTP还有另一个问题
of just just being a Mary it's just very
只是作为一个玛丽而已
simple it supports request response
简单，它支持请求响应
basically if you want to do full
基本上，如果你想做饱
bi-directional communication you know
你知道的双向通讯
that you can't do that with HTTP so you
使用HTTP无法做到这一点，所以您
might do it with a web with WebSockets
可以通过WebSockets在Web上实现
for example WebSockets is a is an
例如WebSockets是一个
interesting option there you might do
您可能会做的有趣的选择
something like server sent events well
像服务器这样的事件可以很好地发送事件
websockets provides message training
websockets提供消息培训
that's it it just provides this
就这样提供
demarcation of payloads over the wire
线上的有效载荷划分
let it allows you to say this is one
让它让你说这是一个
whole thing that's it it doesn't give
整个事情就是这样，它没有给
you any other application-level concerns
您还有其他应用程序级别的顾虑
it's up to the developer to sort of
由开发人员来决定
address that you might do server-sent
您可能会发送服务器的地址
events which is a simple protocol that
事件，这是一个简单的协议，
is textual and porous and you know bama
是文字和多孔的，你知道巴马
the demanding and that does more that
苛刻的要求
does message framing and it's only for
做消息框架，它仅用于
one direction it's server side to client
一个方向是服务器端到客户端
but that's a little bit that's kind of
但这有点像
interesting it also requires on it
有趣的是它也需要
requires text right it's you have to
需要正确的文字，这是你必须
encode binary data in some way that can
以某种方式编码二进制数据
be represented in characters so we have
用字符表示，所以我们有
all these issues right there's all these
所有这些问题就这些
sort of like issues small issues none of
有点像小问题
them particularly huge but you know
他们特别庞大，但你知道
death by a thousand cuts as it were and
死亡人数减少了一千
that matters especially it at Google and
尤其重要的是在Google和
Facebook and Netflix scale right now but
Facebook和Netflix现在可以扩展，但是
that all that might also matter to you
那对你来说可能也很重要
particularly because as I say beyond
特别是因为正如我所说的那样
beyond the concerns of bandwidth and
超出带宽和
efficiency we have just the sort of
效率，我们只是那种
limited and limited nature of HTTP right
HTTP权限的有限性和有限性
what if I want to make a request and
如果我要提出要求怎么办？
then just leave it there just send a
然后就把它放在那里
request and not get the response I'm not
请求而没有得到回应我不是
interested in response I'm not
对回应感兴趣，我不是
interested in the acknowledgement and so
对确认感兴趣，等等
on that's fine forget that's a very
没关系，那是一个非常
common thing to do and a messaging
常见的事情和消息
architecture and there are optimizations
架构和优化
you can make on the infrastructure if
您可以在基础设施上进行
you know that the request was only ever
你知道请求只是
intended to be accepted but never
意欲被接受但从未
responded to right that's a lost
对失去的权利做出回应
opportunity there similarly what about
那里的机会也差不多
you know sending a large amounts of data
你知道发送大量数据
again if you want to send unlimited
再次，如果你想发送无限
streams of data then you're kind of in a
数据流，那么你就有点
pickle here right you uh WebSockets is
泡菜在这里，你啊WebSockets是
an option here but again that has some
这里的一个选择，但同样有一些
limitations and then what if you want to
限制，然后如果您想
do server-side push and client-side push
做服务器端推送和客户端推送
you know like you wanna have a channel a
你知道你想拥有一个频道
bi-directional channel we're both
双向渠道
wearing both sides send potentially
双方都穿可能发送
unlimited streams of data again you
无限的数据流再次
might use WebSockets here but again your
可能在这里使用WebSockets，但再次
list you're missing out on application
列出您错过的申请
semantics have an application level sort
语义具有应用程序级别的排序
of
的
framing semantics and so on so there's
框架语义等等
that and also with HTTP we're so used to
以及HTTP，我们已经习惯了
thinking about it as sort of it's either
考虑它或者是
one response or it's multiple responses
一个响应或多个响应
like with WebSockets it's very easy to
就像使用WebSockets一样，非常容易
or service in events it's very easy to
或服务，这很容易
say I'm going to send a potentially
说我要发送一个潜在的
unlimited stream of data versus I'm
无限的数据流与我
gonna use JSON when these application
这些应用程序将使用JSON
JSON to send this one finite array of
JSON发送此的一个有限数组
data of data with eight records well
有八个记录的数据很好
there doesn't need to be a distinction
无需区分
there it could just be I send one record
那里可能只是我发送一张记录
I send a thousand and if I send a
我寄一千，如果我寄一
thousand then I send it in chunks and
一千然后我把它分块发送
that means that I don't have to wait for
这意味着我不必等待
the whole response to accumulate I can
整个反应积累起来我可以
just start processing it as soon as
尽快开始处理
possible this enables some very
可能这使一些非常
interesting possibilities particularly
特别有趣的可能性
in bandwidth constrained environments a
在带宽受限的环境中
mobile environment etc the other thing
移动环境等
that we're missing in HTTP and other
我们在HTTP和其他版本中缺少的
other protocols is you know the the
其他协议是你知道的
foundational sort of application flow
基本的应用程序流程
control guarantees made by the reactive
反应堆的控制保证
streams write a specification to have
流编写规范以具有
how do you how do you push back on the
你如何将你推回去
producer how do you apply back pressure
生产者你如何施加背压
and when you do have back pressure on
当你确实背压
the you know really you can slow the
你知道你真的可以放慢脚步
rate of consumption the client the
客户的消费率
consumer of the data can slow the rate
数据的使用者会减慢速度
of consumption for the producer by
生产者的消费
requiring or requesting rather less
少要求或少要求
record to the next response that's one
记录下一个响应
with it one thing to do but there's the
要做一件事，但是有
other direction as well right the other
其他方向也正确
direction is if I'm if I am a producer I
方向是如果我是制片人
can send information to the client
可以发送信息给客户
indicating to the consumer rather I can
向消费者表明，我可以
send information to the consumer
发送信息给消费者
indicating what my availability is how
指示我的空房状况如何
much capacity I have you know what my
我有很多能力，你知道我的
uptime you know any kind of interesting
正常运行时间，您知道任何有趣的事情
information whatever that is I want to
信息，无论我想要什么
be able to communicate that to the
能够传达给
consumer to give it an idea of my
消费者给我一个想法
ability to respond to its requests that
回应其要求的能力
would enable load balancing patterns I
将启用负载平衡模式
would enable routing discussions and
将使路由讨论和
decisions right this is this this
正确的决定是这个
communication is something that should
沟通是应该的
be handled at the protocol layer and yet
在协议层进行处理
we so often have to read
我们经常不得不阅读
right so it's much nicer to have this in
对的所以把它放进去会更好
the protocol itself so you can see
协议本身，所以您可以看到
there's a lot of use cases here that are
这里有很多用例
just sort of there's a thousand
差不多有一千
different ways to solve this these
解决这些问题的不同方法
issues but I guess at some point at some
问题，但我想某些时候
point Facebook just said look we we're
点Facebook只是说看我们
trying to graft on top of HTTP and
试图嫁接在HTTP之上
WebSockets and all these other things
WebSockets和所有其他这些东西
application layer concerns when this
应用层关注何时
wasn't meant for that so let's instead
并不是为了这个，所以让我们
try and solve it more efficiently in a
尝试并更有效地解决
different way so our socket seeks to
不同的方式，以便我们的套接字寻求
reduce perceived latency and an
减少感知的延迟并
increased system efficiency by
通过提高系统效率
supporting non-blocking
支持非阻塞
duplex async application communication
双工异步应用程序通信
with flow control over multiple
具有多个流量控制
transports from multiple different
来自多种不同的运输
languages it reduced reduces a hardware
减少的语言减少了硬件
footprint by increasing CPU and memory
通过增加CPU和内存来减少占用空间
efficiency through the use of binary
通过使用二进制效率
encoding and avoiding redundant work by
编码并避免重复工作
allowing persistent connections
允许持久连接
similarly we avoid handshakes in the
同样，我们避免在
associated round trip where possible
关联往返
right and we reduce computation time by
是的，我们减少了计算时间
using binary encoding we allocate less
使用二进制编码，我们分配较少
memory and reduce garbage collection
内存并减少垃圾收集
costs that way so our socket has a lot
这样花费，所以我们的插座有很多
of benefits to it it is ultimately just
的好处，最终只是
a layer five and six or tcp/ip
第五和第六层或tcp / ip
application layer protocol and I think
应用层协议，我认为
it makes it a good choice for
这使其成为一个不错的选择
application developers it's not the only
应用程序开发人员不是唯一的
way you can still use rest you can see
您仍然可以使用休息的方式，您可以看到
you use HTTP that's fine there's a lot
您使用HTTP很好，这有很多
of good stuff there but this is a nice
那里好东西，但这是一个很好
reactive wire protocol and there's a
电抗线协议，有一个
nice API you can use now today we're
不错的API，您今天就可以使用了
gonna look at our socket in the context
要在上下文中查看我们的套接字
of spring actually we're not working
春天的时候我们实际上不工作
that we're gonna use it in a spring
我们将在春季使用它
application but there is no spring
申请但没有春天
integration for it yet okay I say yet
整合还可以，我还说
because we announced a spring one
因为我们宣布了一个春季
platform 2018 that we would have support
我们将提供支持的2018平台
for our socket in Spring Framework 5.2
Spring Framework 5.2中的套接字
there'd be a component model a lot of
会有很多组件模型
spring MVC or the web socket support or
Spring MVC或Web套接字支持或
spring web flex so you'll have a
Spring Web Flex，因此您将拥有一个
compiler model and with that with I
编译器模型，并与我
expect annotations and you know a client
期望注释，并且您认识一个客户
or a template or something along that
或模板或类似的东西
line along those lines
沿着那些线
and you know I'm looking forward to that
你知道我很期待
but it's still useful to kind of take a
但采取某种方式仍然有用
look at it and understand what's
看着它，了解什么
happening so we're gonna use Lum buck
发生了，所以我们要用Lum buck
and that's it that's really all we need
这就是我们真正需要的
I guess we want to use the reactive
我想我们要使用反应式
stuff so I'll bring that in and that's
东西，所以我带进去，那是
it we're just gonna build an app called
我们只是要建立一个名为
our socket and we're gonna hit generate
我们的插座，我们要点击生成
we're using spring boot to that one
我们正在使用 spring boot
which in turn builds upon Spring
反过来建立在Spring之上
Framework 5.1 so not quite there yet not
框架5.1所以还不存在
5.2 okay
5.2好
now we're not gonna spend all day on
现在我们不会花一整天
this though we could don't be thank you
这虽然我们不能谢谢你
all right so what we're gonna do we're
好吧，我们要做的是
gonna build a few applications that
将构建一些应用程序
demonstrate some concepts here we'll
在这里展示一些概念，我们将
start with something very simple let's
从非常简单的事情开始
just say I want to make a request and
只是说我想提出要求，
response but instead of just getting
回应，但不仅仅是得到
their single value back let's call this
他们的单一价值被称为
package our our request response okay
打包我们的请求响应
request response okay and do this
请求响应好，并执行此操作
alright so here we are we have my
好了，所以我们来了
request response type and all I'm gonna
请求响应类型以及所有我要
do is I'm gonna build a simple
我要做的是建立一个简单的
application that that will start up
将启动的应用程序
it'll I'll have two things in here I'm
我会在这里有两件事
gonna have two things that will both
将会有两件事
start up and listen on different ports
启动并在不同的端口上监听
keep in mind of course that those things
当然要记住那些东西
could burn them separate processes these
可以将它们分开燃烧
clients I'm gonna produce a producer and
客户我要生产一个制作人
a consumer and they could run and will
消费者，他们可以并愿意
often run in separate processes but just
通常在单独的流程中运行，但是
to make things clear and to make it
弄清楚并弄清楚
simple and kind of see how these things
简单又有点看这些东西如何
look next to each other
互相看
I find it instructive to develop these
我发现发展这些有启发性
kinds of things in tandem in the same
同一系列中的各种事物
code page and then worry about their
代码页，然后担心他们
their separation two separate processes
他们分开两个独立的过程
separate microservices later on okay so
以后可以单独使用微服务
public static void main string args
公共静态void主字符串args
spring application dot run
春季申请点跑
request/response top-class args okay and
请求/响应顶级参数好
spring good application alright so
春天很好的应用程序好吧
there's our spring would you know
你知道我们的春天吗
scaffolding if you will and from here
脚手架，如果你会和从这里
we're going to develop a producer and a
我们将开发一个制作人和一个
consumer and our producer is gonna be
消费者，我们的生产者将成为
pretty simple it'll be we'll call this a
很简单，我们将其称为
consumer it'll be a spring beam and we
消费者，这将是春天的光芒，我们
want it to start up implements ordered
希望它启动有序的工具
I'll just give it a good news interfaces
我给它一个好消息界面
here because why not because we have
在这里，因为为什么不因为我们有
certain lifecycle issues here so we want
某些生命周期问题，所以我们想要
this to start up later don't so order
这个开始以后不要这样
lowest priority you want this to start
您要开始的最低优先级
up after the server after the producer
在生产者之后的服务器之后
and we'll have a consumer do sir here
先生，我们要请一位消费者来做
class oh do sir ordered and we'll say
上课哦，先生下令，我们会说
order dot highest precedence all right
顺序点最高优先级可以
so pretty clear right now we want the
现在非常清楚，我们想要
producer to respond to incoming requests
生产者响应传入的请求
so I'm gonna listen for an event and you
所以我要听一个事件，你
could use the annotation here at MIT
可以在麻省理工学院使用注释
mister I often do but it doesn't matter
我经常做的先生，没关系
in this case and I've already got a few
在这种情况下，我已经有一些
interfaces okay there we go
接口好了，我们去了
so I'm gonna listen for that event and
所以我要听那个事件
when that event happens I'm gonna start
当那件事发生时，我要开始
serving data using our socket and again
使用我们的套接字再次提供数据
we're gonna use the low level our socket
我们将使用较低级别的套接字
API so there's nothing really fancy here
API，所以这里没有什么特别的
it's just a very simple API that looks
这只是一个看起来非常简单的API
like any other network API you've
就像您拥有的任何其他网络API
probably with what you are probably
可能与你可能
already familiar we're gonna create a
已经很熟悉了，我们将创建一个
thing that will respond with a stream of
会以
data just an arbitrary reactive stream
数据只是任意反应流
and I mean like I'm just gonna use
我的意思是说我只是要用
reactor right and by the way I need to
反应堆的权利，顺便说一句，我需要
comment this out I'm gonna bring in the
发表评论，我要带
spring mood starter but we don't need
春天的心情启动器，但我们不需要
this
这个
Dewey you know probably safe let's just
杜威，您知道可能很安全，
leave that in there just in case so I'm
留在那儿以防万一
gonna build a producer the producer is
要建立一个生产者，生产者是
going to listen for incoming requests so
将要监听传入的请求，所以
our socket factory know I want to add
我们的插座工厂知道我要添加
the our second dependencies first
我们第二个依赖
alright so we have to do that if I've
好吧，如果我有，我们必须这样做
gotten ahead of myself have a nice so
超越自己有一个很好的
we're gonna add the different
我们将添加不同的
dependencies here
这里的依赖
usually when you add our socket you
通常当您添加我们的插座时
don't have to worry about you know it's
不必担心您知道
safe to use these two demands he's that
可以安全地使用这两个要求，他就是
we're gonna use the our socket to a
我们将使用我们的插座
socket transport to let's see here it is
套接字传输让我们看这里
dependency and it is these up article
依赖，这是这些文章
keep for me our socket transport nitty
为我保持插座运输的整洁
and we want to use all eleven fourteen
我们要用全部十一十四
and I think Oh 11 okay and I hope that
我想哦11好的，我希望
brings in the core yes over compile time
在编译时引入核心是
so we can just bring in
所以我们可以带进去
okay all right there's a
好吧，好吧，有一个
okay alright so there's our socket um
好吧，所以我们有插座
here we go
开始了
now our socket factory dot receive dots
现在我们的插座工厂点接收点
socket acceptor now the socket acceptor
插座接受器现在插座接受器
is fairly straight this is actually
很直，这实际上是
where the meat of the work happens so
工作的实质发生在哪里
we're gonna move that out here I'm gonna
我们要把它移到这里，我要
say socket acceptor and our job when
说套接字接受器和我们的工作
somebody makes a request is to provide a
有人要求提供
publisher and mono just a wrapper around
发布者和mono只是一个包装
an our socket and so what you're given
我们的插座，所以您得到了什么
is the incoming sender our socket and
是传入的发件人我们的套接字，
here's an you setup metadata if you want
这是您要设置的元数据
it and you're you know you can return a
它，你知道你可以返回一个
brand new our socket here and that's
全新我们的插座在这里
what we're gonna do we're gonna come
我们要做什么我们要来
back to this in a second okay so to do
再过一遍再做一次
and here it's gonna be the socket
这是插座
acceptor I'm gonna use a transport now
承兑人，我现在要使用交通工具
here I usually use the TCP server
在这里我通常使用TCP服务器
transport but keep in mind our socket
运输，但请记住我们的插座
doesn't care you know it's in to a point
不在乎你知道它在某种程度上
it's actually protocol agnostic it's
它实际上是与协议无关的
transport agnostic so remember I said
运输不可知的所以记得我说过
earlier that WebSockets are appealing
早些时候WebSocket颇具吸引力
for certain use cases but they don't
对于某些用例，但它们没有
have application level semantics well
具有应用程序级别的语义
you can you can fix that there's
你可以解决这个问题
actually a WebSocket transport right web
实际上是一个WebSocket传输权网站
so good transport that server transport
很好的运输，服务器运输
there you go dot create seven thousand
你去那里创造七千
one two for example so you could use
一两个，例如，您可以使用
this one instead right and you can now
相反，这是对的，您现在可以
communicate over WebSocket over the same
通过WebSocket进行相同的通信
protocol and port and it'll do the
协议和端口，它将完成
message payment but everything else is
消息支付，但其他一切
done in terms of our socket so so you
就我们的插座而言，所以您
can do that if you want that makes it
可以做到这一点，如果你想要做到这一点
easier to integrate this into our
轻松将其整合到我们的
environments that the only speak web
只讲网络的环境
socket but I'm gonna use TCP because
套接字，但我要使用TCP，因为
it's it's fast and it works and it's we
这是快速的，而且有效，是我们
have no reason to use WebSockets in this
没有理由在此使用WebSockets
particular case then I'm gonna start the
特殊情况下，我将开始
the code I'm gonna block on the response
我将在响应中阻止的代码
on there under the server okay
在服务器下的那里好
now the actual work as you can see here
现在您可以在这里看到实际的工作
is producing this our socket so this is
正在生产我们的插座，所以这是
easy you just say I'm gonna return a new
容易，您只是说我要退货
abstract our socket
抽象我们的套接字
okay
好的
and they say return monotype just
他们说只返回单型
abstract and this meant this class there
抽象的，这意味着那里的课程
we go
我们去
this class has a few methods here you
这个课有几种方法
can see you see our socket is very
可以看到你看到我们的插座非常
flexible you can see it is transport
灵活，您可以看到它是运输工具
agnostic you can see it supports
不可知论者可以看到它的支持
multiple message exchange patterns
多种消息交换模式
fire-and-forget request response
即发即弃请求响应
requests trinium and request channel and
请求三年期和请求渠道，以及
metadata push and we'll come back to all
元数据推送，我们将回到所有
those in a second and it supports
那些在一秒钟，它支持
different encoding is that or rather it
还是不同的编码
doesn't specify an encoding of the data
没有指定数据的编码
in the payload so when you send data
在有效负载中，因此当您发送数据时
from one producer to one consumer they
从一个生产者到一个消费者
must agree our priori on the encoding of
必须同意我们的先验编码
that data you could actually you know
您实际上可以知道的数据
you could send but everyone could send
你可以发送，但每个人都可以发送
JSON you can send Google protocol
可以发送JSON的JSON协议
buffers you could do whatever you want
缓冲区，您可以做任何您想做的
there's no no requirement here that you
这里没有要求你
do one thing or the other and everything
做一件事情或另一件事
gets hurried back and forth in terms of
急于来回
these payload envelope objects it's just
这些有效载荷包络对象
bytes these are byte buffers basically
字节这些基本上是字节缓冲区
um now let's look at this this
嗯，现在让我们看看这个
fire-and-forget method says that the
解雇法说
producer oh sorry the consumer is going
生产者哦，抱歉消费者要去
to send a request to us and we're gonna
向我们发送请求，我们将
we're gonna we're gonna acknowledge the
我们将要承认
request so we're these are callback
请求，所以我们这些是回调
methods that get called when somebody
当某人被调用的方法
sends a when a client sends a request to
客户端发送请求到时发送
us as the service okay so the
我们作为服务还可以，所以
fire-and-forget method expects a payload
即发即弃方法需要有效载荷
a payload is just a single value just
有效载荷只是一个值而已
one value it could be a byte it could be
一个值，可能是一个字节，可能是
a string it could be whatever you want
一个字符串，它可以是任何您想要的
right it can be serialize Java object
可以序列化Java对象
you know don't do that but it could be I
你知道不要那样做，但是可能是我
mean it could be whatever you want but
意味着可以随便你
the point is that is just one single
关键是那只是一个
thing and your job is just accept it
事情，你的工作就是接受它
process it do whatever you need to do
处理您需要做的一切
with it but you don't get to send a
它，但你没有发送
response back the response is just mono
回应回来回应只是单声道
to avoid which you can get by calling
避免通过致电获得
dot ven right
点右
so on most reactive most reactor
所以反应最活跃的反应堆
reactive streams you can just call dot
反应性的流，你可以只点
then so that's one option
那是一种选择
request response is also very
请求响应也很
straightforward this is this is more
直接，这是更多
natural this is I think if you're in
自然，这是我想，如果你在
doubt you might start with this right
怀疑你可能会从这项权利开始
request response just says I'm expecting
请求响应只是说我在期待
to send a single release a single
发送单个发行单
payload to the server and I'm expecting
有效负载到服务器，我期望
a single payload back so it's one value
一个有效载荷返回，所以它是一个价值
in one value out request stream is where
一值进出请求流在哪里
things start to get more interesting and
事情开始变得越来越有趣，
more more stateful right you've got now
您现在拥有更多有状态的权利
here you've got a publisher that you're
在这里，您有一家发布商
sending back to the client so the client
发送回客户端，以便客户端
sends you a request for the payload and
向您发送有效载荷请求，并
then you send back a publisher and you
然后您发回发布者，您
notice that these are Manos and fluxes
注意这些是Manos和通量
these are from reactor this is not just
这些来自反应堆，而不仅仅是
job you know that this is not just the
您知道这不仅是工作
erectus dreams publisher these are
勃起梦的出版商这些是
actually specific subtypes from reactor
实际上来自反应堆的特定亚型
that are built into this Fitness
健身中内置的
protocol this project from Facebook so
从Facebook协议这个项目，所以
here you know imagine you're doing to
在这里你知道想象你正在做
find all or you're doing a you know get
找到全部或您正在做的你知道
stock ticker updates or something so you
股票行情更新或诸如此类的东西
could say send me all the stock ticker
可以说把所有股票行情发给我
updates for the stock you know whatever
您知道的股票更新
and then the stocks ticker symbol is
然后股票代码为
what you send in the payload and the the
您在有效载荷中发送的内容以及
flux is the updates every second or
通量是每秒更新一次
whatever every heartbeat event
不管每一次心跳事件
indicating all the new updates right and
指示所有新的更新，并且
then finally you've got sort of complete
最后，您已经完成了
back and forth you know a bi-directional
来回你知道双向
channel and then in this case you send a
频道，然后在这种情况下，您发送一个
stream of values and you get back a
价值流，你得到一个
stream your bodies right so that's very
正确地流走你的身体，这非常
convenient as well and then this one
方便，然后这一个
isn't a it's you you don't usually use
不是你通常不使用的你
this to communicate data back and forth
这样来回交流数据
this is more about communicating
这更多是关于交流
availability this is more about leasing
可用性，这更多是关于租赁
you know telling the telling the the
你知道告诉
the requestor you know pushing back on
您知道的请求者会继续执行
the requestor and supposed to pushing
请求者，应该推
back on the producer okay so let's just
回到制作人，好吧，让我们
try something that remember
尝试记住的东西
fire-and-forget is nice if you want to
抛弃式的遗忘很好，如果你想
send data and that you want to make sure
发送数据并且您要确保
that the machinery can I'm both the
机械既可以
producer in the consumer can dismantle
消费者中的生产者可以拆除
itself as quickly as possible and you
自己尽快，你
know to alleviates tape so you can use
知道减轻胶带，因此您可以使用
that one request the response is fairly
那个请求的响应是相当
straightforward so I guess that's well
简单明了，所以我想那很好
just let you sort of explore that one
只是让您有点探索
yourself
你自己
let's do request stream so we're gonna
让我们请求流，以便我们
make a request I'm gonna send back a
提出要求，我要寄回
stream of values okay so we're gonna
价值流好吧，我们要
assume somebody's gonna request us
假设有人会要求我们
somebody's gonna connect to port 7,000
有人要连接到端口7,000
on our server and when they do they're
在我们的服务器上，当他们这样做时
gonna they're gonna run into this our
他们会遇到这个我们的
socket factor which is listening there
在那里监听的套接字因子
it's gonna invoke the socket acceptor
它会调用套接字接受器
which is going to then be charged with
然后将被指控
producing this abstract our socket which
产生这个摘要我们的套接字
we send back right that's the thing
我们发回正确的东西
that's going to be put into service to
将会投入使用
listen to and respond to the sender and
听取并回复发件人，并且
what we send back can be anything we
我们发回的东西可以是任何东西
want right I can let's just imagine you
想要吧，我可以想象你
have a service that produces a string of
有一个产生字符串的服务
values okay a publisher of string a
值可以，字符串a的发布者
stream of strings as well so notify
字符串流也是如此，因此请通知
notifications okay and so we're just
通知还可以，所以我们只是
gonna do a very common thing you've seen
会做一件你见过的很普通的事
me do this before I'm sure it's return
在确定返回之前，我先执行此操作
stream of or generate even this will be
流甚至生成这将是
a new supplier and it gets a supplier of
一个新的供应商，它得到了
string and I'm going to say return hello
字符串，我要说回声你好
at instant dot now dot to string and
现在点立即点到字符串并
that'll be a publisher from a stream
将会成为信息流中的发布者
okay
好的
good okay look at that so there's my
好吧，好吧，那是我的
never-ending stream of data and you know
永无止境的数据流，您知道
I'm gonna delay this I'm actually insert
我要延迟一下，我实际上要插入
a second long pause between each
彼此之间有一秒钟的长时间停顿
published emitted item and that would be
发布的发射项目，那将是
the the publisher I'm gonna send back so
我要发回的出版商
let's just gonna send a flux of string
让我们发送一连串的字符串
and this could be anything it could be a
这可能是任何东西
you know a custom object or a foo or a
您知道自定义对象或foo或a
bar whatever you could you know as long
只要你知道就禁止
as you can get it into a payload so our
因为您可以将其放入有效载荷中，所以我们
job is to take the publisher of string
工作是接受字符串的发布者
and turn it into a publisher of payloads
并变成有效载荷的发布者
and that's pretty straightforward
这很简单
because once you can get this object of
因为一旦你可以得到这个对象
yours into bytes or into a string it's
您的字节或字符串
fairly it's just it's easy from there
从那里很容易
right in this case maybe we can have the
在这种情况下，也许我们可以拥有
name what I think about that on this so
如此命名我对此的想法
let's actually have a screen name okay
让我们实际使用一个屏幕名称
I'm gonna say hello name at this time
我现在要打个招呼
okay
好的
not bad so we're gonna greet the
不错，所以我们要问候
requester with their own name okay so
有自己名字的请求者好吧
here I'm going to say payload don't get
在这里我要说的是有效载荷没有得到
utf-8 data utf-8 that's the string you
utf-8数据utf-8是您的字符串
can see that we can get a byte buffer so
可以看到我们可以得到一个字节缓冲区
if you wanted to but I want the utf-8
如果您想但我想要utf-8
data so I'll get that back okay and
数据，这样我就可以恢复正常，
we're gonna send this back we're gonna
我们要寄回给我们
say name and the values that we send
说出姓名和我们发送的值
back will be returned notifications for
返回将返回有关的通知
the name and we can get back a publisher
名称，我们可以找回出版商
so one take the publisher of greetings
所以请大家问候一下
and turn it into a publisher of payloads
并变成有效载荷的发布者
okay
好的
default payload dark rate breathing okay
默认有效负载暗率呼吸还可以
there's that that can be a lambda method
那可能是lambda方法
reference even there go not bad right so
参考即使没有不好就这样
all we're doing back on default crate
我们在默认箱子上所做的一切
and you can see I shouldn't have got
你会看到我不应该有
gone so quick default rate takes a
如此之快的默认利率需要
default payload crate takes a byte
默认有效载荷箱占用一个字节
buffer it takes a byte buffer my buffer
缓冲区需要一个字节缓冲区我的缓冲区
it takes a payload it takes a car
它需要一个有效载荷，它需要一辆汽车
sequence so I'm just using I'm relying
顺序，所以我只是在使用我依赖
upon the the variant that takes the
在采用
string the car sequence okay so I'm just
串好车序列好吧，我就是
saying string okay and that collapse is
说字符串好，然后崩溃是
nicely into that and that's it that's
很好，就是这样
our server okay and this is fairly I
我们的服务器还可以，这相当我
think we can agree this is fairly
认为我们可以同意这是相当公平的
straightforward
直截了当
you can even rewrite it as a lambda
您甚至可以将其重写为lambda
that's nice so there's our producer and
很好，所以有我们的制作人
we have this very simple trivial example
我们有这个非常简单的例子
but if Ken where can you get a publisher
但是如果肯（肯）在哪里可以找到出版商
of T from well any of your spring data
任何弹簧数据中的T
projects of support reactive programming
支持反应式编程的项目
right the spring data reactive MongoDB
对 spring data 反应性MongoDB
the spring data reactive Redis and
spring data 反应式Redis和
Couchbase in Cassandra you can use our
您可以在Cassandra中使用Couchbase
two DBC the reactive sequel data access
两个DBC反应式续集数据访问
layer the spray the nascent spring data
分层喷涂新生的弹簧数据
or TBC project supports this as well so
或者TBC项目也支持这一点
we can do all sorts of interesting
我们可以做各种有趣的事情
things we can source data from a number
我们可以从大量数据中获取数据的东西
of different places and indeed we could
不同的地方，实际上我们可以
act as the consumer here you know we can
充当消费者，您知道我们可以
we could be consuming data from one
我们可能会消耗一个
micro service transforming it and then
微服务对其进行转换，然后
sending it on and to another
发送到另一个
microservice we can act as a bridge it's
微服务，我们可以充当桥梁
very natural to do that kind of thing
做这样的事情很自然
since we have just publishers are going
因为我们只有出版商
back and forth right or from hither and
来回来回或从
now so we can do all sorts of
现在，我们可以做各种
interesting things here that's our
有趣的事情就是我们
produce from now the consumer side is
从现在开始消费方
similarly easy so we say it's gonna be
同样容易，所以我们说它将
an application with its inner
具有内部功能的应用程序
application ready event and on the
应用就绪事件以及
consumer side we're going to say that we
消费者方面，我们要说的是
want to start up a new are sausage
想开始一个新的香肠
factory we're going to connect using the
工厂，我们将使用
TCP client transport not the server
TCP客户端传输而不是服务器
transport
运输
on port 7,000 I'm gonna start the
在7,000端口上，我将开始
request I'm gonna flatmap many we're
要求我要绘制许多我们的地图
gonna gonna do we're gonna say once
我们要说一次
we've connected we were giving it back
我们已经连接好了，我们还给了它
on our socket client instance once we're
在我们的套接字客户端实例上
doing that I'm going to subscribe or
这样做，我要订阅或
better yet with the block or just
更好的与块或只是
subscribe I guess okay once we're doing
订阅我想我们一旦做好就可以了
that let's say our socket dot and
假设我们的插座点和
request a bit of data so we're gonna
要求一些数据，所以我们要
send a request with our client our
与我们的客户发送请求
socket our send a right that's what this
插入我们的发送权限，这就是这个
is actually you know you should think of
其实你知道你应该想到
this as being the sender our socket
这是发送者，我们的套接字
instance when we do that we're going to
实例，当我们这样做时，我们将
send our name so let's bring tips all
发送我们的名字，让我们带来所有提示
right so we're gonna send that stream
对，所以我们要发送该流
and when we do that we can get a
当我们这样做时，我们可以获得
response back and the response that
回应和回应
we're gonna get back is a payload that
我们要回来的是一个有效载荷
we're going to turn into string of
我们将变成一串
course we're gonna take out the string
当然我们要去掉弦
value there and from there I suppose we
我认为从那里开始有价值
could just log each guy go huh what else
可以记录每个人去吧，还有什么
to subscribe they do all sorts of things
订阅他们做各种事情
so do on next log info and I'm gonna
所以在下一个日志信息上做，我要
just log the results log4j to already so
只需将结果log4j记录到已经这样
each value that comes back we're gonna
每个返回的价值我们都会
log it out okay or you know actually
将其注销好吧，或者您实际上知道
just here result love that info
就在这里结果爱那个信息
processing
处理中
new results okay
新结果还可以
very cool so there we go there's our our
非常酷，所以我们去那里是我们的
new results coming back from the server
服务器返回新结果
with different times okay
在不同的时间还可以
good so there's that let's now run this
好，所以现在让我们运行这个
and see what happens
看看会发生什么
oops
哎呀
was there somebody already there that's
已经有人在那儿了吗
just Christ mm or 7001 because oh seven
只是基督毫米或7001，因为哦，七
haha that's actually correct so 700 is a
哈哈，实际上是正确的，所以700是一个
I need to be running as a route to do
我需要跑步作为路线
that but 7000 well that's easy so let's
那不过7000井，这很容易，所以让我们
just fix that okay close this and that
只要修复好吧就可以关闭
there we go so it's gonna you know it's
我们去那里，所以你会知道
where the client the consumer is
消费者在哪里
processing the message hello string tips
处理消息你好字符串提示
wing tips and that message is being sent
机翼提示，该消息正在发送
out every second 50 51 52 53 etc etc etc
每秒输出50 51 52 53等等等等等
so that's a very simple example of where
所以这是一个非常简单的例子
we're making a request from getting a
我们正在通过获取一个请求
stream of data back it could have been a
返回的数据流可能是
publisher with just one value certainly
当然只有一种价值的出版商
right this is a you know you've seen
对，这是你知道的
this before right that's that would be
在此之前，那将是
easy but it's kind of more interesting
容易，但更有趣
to look at how we can do a reactive
看看我们如何做一个反应
stream back all right now this is fairly
现在流回所有这是相当
straightforward let's take a look at a
简单的让我们看一下
slightly more involved example all right
稍微多一点的例子好吧
let's talk about duplex sort of channels
让我们谈谈双工通道
okay and here I'm gonna play a game of
好的，在这里我要玩
ping pong and this will just be back and
乒乓球，这将回来，
forth as always so public static
一如既往地如此公共静态
look at me go alright got that spring
看着我，好吧，那年春天
boot application and we're gonna say
启动应用程序，我们要说
spring application but run ping-pong dot
春季申请但运行乒乓点
class orgs alright so there's our
班级组织不错，所以我们有
application and we have two things are
应用程序，我们有两件事是
gonna happen here we have the ping and
会发生在这里，我们有ping和
with the pong and this is a spring beam
与乒乓球，这是弹簧梁
as is that and this would be an
这样，这将是一个
application listener application ready
应用程序监听器已准备就绪
event okay open that okay
事件好吗打开那好
just copy paste some code here to make
只要复制粘贴一些代码在这里
things go a little quicker alright so
事情进展得更快一点，所以
the ping even though it's ping the ping
ping即使ping通
is the client the pong is the server
是客户端，是服务器
that's the thing that responds after the
那就是在
first request has been made so the pong
第一个请求已经发出，所以乒乓球
really we should we want to make sure
真的，我们应该确保
that gets started up first right so
首先开始吧，所以
ordered
下令
okay okay
好吧好吧
ordered dot highest precedence
点的最高优先级
and the
和
ordered here returned order dot Louis
在这里订购返回的订购点Louis
present very cool
现在很酷
okay so pong has to start up first we
好，所以乒乓球必须先启动
want that to be the case and now we're
希望情况如此，现在我们
going to send we're gonna send a request
要发送，我们将发送请求
for the to the server and we're gonna
为服务器，我们要
get a response back and were just gonna
得到回应，只会
keep updating each other we're gonna do
不断更新彼此，我们要做
a little simple state machine that's
一个简单的状态机
gonna look at the reese look at the
要看里斯看
incoming request and then based on that
传入请求，然后基于该请求
request send back either a ping or pong
请求发回乒乓球或乒乓球
okay so let's extract that up logic out
好吧，让我们提取出逻辑
until a single place here static string
直到这里一个单一的静态字符串
reply string in and say if in dot equals
回复字符串并说点是否等于
ignore case ping then we return oh yeah
忽略大小写ping，然后我们返回哦，是的
in dot equals ignore case pong return
点等于等于忽略大小写返回
pink simple right otherwise throw a new
粉红色的简单的权利，否则抛出一个新的
illegal argument exception incoming
非法参数异常传入
value must be either pink or okay good
值必须是粉红色或还可以
so there's my simple ping-pong reply
所以有我简单的乒乓球回复
method uh now let's implement ping first
方法现在让我们先实现ping
because that's arguably more more fun i
因为那可以说更有趣，我
guess it easier huh and it's all pretty
猜它更容易吧，一切都很漂亮
good but this one's them this one's a
好，但是这是他们这是一个
good place to start since just the first
从第一次开始就开始的好地方
one on the code page let's first of all
首先在代码页上
create a logger so we have something
创建一个记录器，以便我们有一些东西
which is to log and i'll announce that
要记录的日志，我会宣布
we are starting the application up so
我们正在启动应用程序，所以
log dot starting this class not get name
开始该类的日志点未获取名称
and what we're gonna do is gonna say our
我们要做的就是说我们的
socket factory dot connect dot transport
插座工厂点连接点运输
eliminates of tcp client-side transport
消除了tcp客户端传输
create listen important seven thousand
创造重要的七千听
and by the way there's a host you can
顺便说一句，你可以
specify there as well and you can bind
在那里也指定，您可以绑定
to a certain IP address etc but
到某个IP地址等，但是
I'm just gonna go to you know zero zero
我只是去找你知道零零
zero zero and 7000 start flatmap many
零零和7000开始平面图很多
get a socket okay so this is all fairly
得到一个插座好，所以这一切都相当
familiar you've done this before then
熟悉的您在此之前已完成此操作
dot block please make sure we get that
点块，请确保我们得到了
right now given the socket we're gonna
现在给定套接字，我们要
send a request for a channel followed by
发送频道请求，然后发送
directional stream of data so here in
定向数据流，所以在这里
the channel I'm gonna send a request at
我要在的频道发送请求
an interval okay I'm gonna say flux dot
间隔好吧，我要说通量点
interval duration of seconds one dot map
一秒点图的间隔时间
okay I and turn this into a default
好吧，我把它变成默认
payload that crate
装在箱子里的有效载荷
okay okay and I'm gonna map that into
好吧好吧，我要映射到
you know when we get when we make that
你知道我们什么时候做的
request let's see here
请求让我们看看这里
is that right we're gonna request a
就是这样，我们要
channel yeah that looks right okay so in
是的，看起来不错，所以在
a request channel and we're gonna map
请求频道，我们将进行地图
each response it comes back into a
每个回应都会返回一个
string like so I'm going to map each one
像这样的字符串，所以我要映射每个
of those I just want to mount each one
我只想装每个的
of those log that info received string
这些日志中，信息接收到字符串
in get class don't get name I'm just
在上课时不要叫我名字
gonna just take ten of these okay so we
就拿其中的十个好吧，所以我们
don't want to run forever and then
不想永远跑然后
finally you know one thing you should do
最后你知道你应该做的一件事
it I didn't do it last one do finally
我最后没有做
is disposed okay all right so what's
被安排好吧，那是什么
happening here let's look at that code
发生在这里，让我们看一下这段代码
here don't look at that
这里不要看
all right did that work so we've got now
没事，所以我们现在有了
a publisher that's producing a new value
产生新价值的出版商
every 10 seconds
每10秒
it's producing a new value every 10
每10产生一个新的价值
seconds MC what am I doing wrong here
秒MC我在做什么错
interval good gonna map that okay good
间隔好，要映射好吗
Oh tag I was trying to take not tag
哦，标签，我试图不标签
what's okay there we go I'm sitting
没关系，我们去坐
there staring at the obvious hair
盯着明显的头发
alright so we've got this now let's see
好吧，现在我们有了这个，让我们看看
that's the the basic code for the ping
这是ping的基本代码
basically in the pong side and the palm
基本上在乒乓球和掌心
side we have a little bit more
一边，我们还有一点
intelligence here we have to have a
情报在这里，我们必须有一个
little bit more intelligence Oh
多一点智慧哦
naturally
自然
so let's do that here in the in the pong
所以我们在乒乓球里做
side we're gonna listen for our socket
一边我们要听我们的插座
factory don't you see you dot acceptor
工厂你没有看到你的点受体
and we're gonna use our self as a socket
我们将把自己当作一个插座
acceptor first all right good and this
接受者首先好，这个
transport TCP server transport create
传输TCP服务器传输创建
7,000 dot start dot subscribe alright so
7,000点开始点订阅好
there's the there's that and then the
那里有那个，然后
work of actually sitting in the socket
实际坐在插座上的工作
back that's what we do what we do here
这就是我们在这里做的事
and we say mono that we wanna create a
我们说单声道我们想创建一个
new abstract our socket right just like
新摘要我们的套接字就像
before
之前
so and we're gonna request a channel ok
所以我们要请求一个频道
so monotype just
所以单字型
RS okay and in this response say a flux
RS很好，在这个回应中说了一个通量
dot from payloads map payload get
负载点映射负载
negative eight up to on next let's log
负八位，直到下一个让我们记录
this out a string here
这是一个字符串
stream Oh get class the lager annotation
流哦，获取类的更大的注解
there already and map the value that we
已经存在并映射我们的价值
got using ping pong
开始使用乒乓球
I'm going to turn that into a payload
我要把它变成有效载荷
ok what's in the whole thing back so
好吧，整个事情又回来了吗
there we go that's the whole that's it
我们去的就是全部
that's I mean I love that that's right
我是说我爱那是对的
that's very simple so we're saying when
这很简单，所以我们说什么时候
somebody requests a channel with values
有人请求带有值的渠道
in it we're going to take a when take
在它里面，我们要花点时间
the publisher and turn it into a flux
发布者，并将其转变为潮流
then we have to take each value in that
那么我们必须将其中的每个价值
publisher of incoming payloads turn it
传入负载的发布者将其转过来
into a string and log out what we
到一个字符串，然后注销我们
received and then we're gonna create a
收到，然后我们将创建一个
response for that so if the string that
因此，如果字符串
we received is ping then we're gonna
我们收到的是ping然后我们要
send back over a pong or visa versa and
通过乒乓球发回，反之亦然
then we're gonna send the response back
然后我们将回复发送回去
ok
好
and you know in reality I could have
你知道我实际上可以
done the same kind of I could have
做过我可能曾经做过的事情
called reply here right that would be
在这里打电话回覆
fine as well I could have done that I
我也可以做到
could have looked at the you know I
本可以看着你知道的我
could have done a lot a whole number of
本来可以做很多很多的
things here too to process that but we
这里的事情也可以处理，但是我们
already know it's gonna be that so let's
已经知道这将是那样，让我们
and I'm much more interesting as seeing
我更有趣的是
where it's happening what's happening in
发生了什么事
and when okay so when we do that and
好的，所以当我们这样做时，
this is the ping pong application so
这是乒乓球应用程序，所以
I'll start that one instead
我会开始那个
there we are so it'll continue for 10
我们在那里，所以它将继续10
cycles one hopes
循环一个希望
okay so isn't that cool
好吧，那不是很酷
so in receives pong obviously so the
所以很明显收到乒乓球
first thing that I got sent is received
我收到的第一件事已收到
ping in pong right and then we sent back
ping in pong，然后我们发回
pong which was acknowledged here in ping
乒乓球在这里被承认
and then we received ping etc right so
然后我们收到ping等，这样
you can see the back and forth the ball
你可以看到来回的球
moving back and forth across the two
在两个方向上来回移动
different producers and consumers so
不同的生产者和消费者
hopefully you've got some appreciation
希望你有所感激
for what's possible here now this is a
因为现在这里可能
as yet nascent protocol there's all
到目前为止，尚有所有协议
sorts of interesting possibilities this
各种有趣的可能性
is the beginning of course as with all
是所有课程的开始
things will start in Spring Framework
一切将从Spring Framework开始
5.2 will see support there the our
5.2将会看到我们的支持
socket website our socket github here
套接字网站我们的套接字github在这里
our socket itself have some interesting
我们的插座本身有一些有趣的地方
stuff coming right there's a cotton
东西来了，那里有棉花
binding apparently coming there's a
绑定显然要来了
botnet implementation coming that's
僵尸网络实现即将到来
pretty cool different transports one of
很酷的不同运输之一
which supports Aaron which is a super
支持超级的亚伦
super fast protocol that was developed
开发的超快速协议
by Martin Thompson among others and you
马丁·汤普森（Martin Thompson）等人与您
know if you want something that is
知道你是否想要的是
absolutely sympathetic to the machine
绝对同情机器
that this protocol doesn't it doesn't
这个协议不，不是
get much better than this one so this is
比这个要好得多，所以这是
a transport that you can use if you want
您可以使用的交通工具
you just add the libraries and use that
您只需添加库并使用
there's a a let me see there's a Python
有一个让我看到有一个Python
and go bindings that are I'm not sure
然后去我不确定的绑定
there's any progress been made on there
那里取得了任何进展
but that's interesting
但这很有趣
there was as far as I can remember a
据我所记得，有一个
load balancer
负载均衡器
repositories
仓库
or sucking let's see our second Java oh
还是吮吸，让我们看看我们的第二个爪哇哦
yeah there's a load balancing examples
是的，有一个负载均衡的例子
there's a load mounts for that's in the
那里有一个负载支架
works that's very populous that bodes
人口众多的作品
very well there's micrometer intubation
很好，有千分尺插管
so you can actually capture metrics and
因此您实际上可以捕获指标并
you we've talked about micrometer and in
您我们已经谈到了千分尺
previous installment of spring tips I
上一期的 spring 技巧 I
encourage you to find that video and
鼓励您找到该视频，
watch that to learn more about
观看以了解更多信息
micrometer also - good stuff you know
千分尺-您知道的好东西
coming and more examples in fact you
来了，事实上更多的例子
know I I based some of what we talked
知道II基于我们所说的一些内容
about today on ideas reckoning from this
关于今天的想法
example so if you want more examples you
例如，如果您想要更多示例
should donate to solve this code but
应该捐赠解决这个代码，但是
also watch this space so our socket lady
还看这个空间，所以我们的插座女士
right that's you know interesting watch
对，那你知道有趣的手表
the space though because we're gonna
空间，因为我们要
have like I say in spring from core 5.2
就像我在春季从核心5.2所说的那样
we should have an intubation for our
我们应该为我们插管
socket in the framework itself as it
套接字本身在框架中
with a component model that's a bit more
组件模型要多一点
high-level a bit more sort of naturally
高级一点自然地
mapped to your business object into your
映射到您的业务对象到您的
business domain then for example our
那么我们的业务领域
socket factor connected whatever um by
插座系数通过um连接
the by you know you would normally I
你知道你通常会
only had one client my my consumer in
我的消费者只有一个客户
this case was ping and it only made one
这个案子是坪，只有一个
request ever but you would normally
曾经要求，但您通常会
wouldn't you wouldn't normally do that
您通常不会那样做吗
normally you'd start yet you know in
通常你会开始，但是你知道
your constructor you start thick the the
您的构造函数开始
our socket client and then whenever you
我们的套接字客户端，然后每当您
need to make a request
需要提出要求
whenever somebody whenever a client
每当有人，每当客户
makes a request you get a pointer to the
发出请求，您将获得一个指向
our socket client and make a request
我们的套接字客户端并提出请求
right so this is their this is your
对，所以这是他们，这是你的
gateway if you will to the or socket
网关（如果要连接到或套接字）
service so you would source this stash
服务，因此您将采购此藏匿处
this initialize it in the constructor
这会在构造函数中对其进行初始化
and then use it over and over um
然后一遍又一遍地使用它
all right with that my friends I hope
我希望我的朋友们都可以
you got something out of this I hope
我希望你从中得到一些东西
you'll check out the website I hope
你会检查我希望的网站
you'll follow along as we introduce this
您将按照我们的介绍进行操作
in the in the year 2019 we'll have a
在2019年，我们将有一个
better and bigger support for our socket
更好，更大的插座支持
in the framework proper and I hope
在适当的框架中，我希望
you'll consider the possibilities you
你会考虑你的可能性
know you can do reactive sequel data
知道你可以做反应性续集数据
access you've got reactive a web socket
访问您具有反应性的Web套接字
you've got reactive web flux for HTTP
您具有用于HTTP的反应式Web流量
now you've got our socket what a time to
现在您已经有了我们的插座，什么时间
be alive all based on the underpinnings
基于基础而活着
of reactor I had the reactor framework
我拥有反应堆框架
and by the way I want to stress this is
而且我想强调的是
this is not the only way to do reactor
这不是做反应堆的唯一方法
based RPC right now
现在基于RPC
but it is my favorite is I think the one
但我最喜欢的是
with the most potential alternatively
最具潜力的
there are some people that might be
有些人可能是
interested in the GRP C compiler from
对GRP C编译器感兴趣
Facebook right Facebook has a no it's re
Facebook权利Facebook没有
from Salesforce Salesforce have a GRP C
来自Salesforce Salesforce的GRP C
compiler a pro talk compiler plug-in
编译器专业人士编译器插件
that then generates reactor based
然后生成基于反应堆的
services which you know that's kind of
您知道的那种服务
interesting but of course that wick that
有趣，但当然那
limits you to the limitations of G RPC
限制您使用G RPC的限制
which is to say it runs on top of HTTP 2
也就是说，它运行在HTTP 2之上
and it it assumes that you want to use
它假设您要使用
Google Google protocol buffers and so
Google Google协议缓冲区等
you know it can be kind of limiting plus
你知道这可能会限制
it you know it's not I don't think it's
你知道不是我不认为是
nearly some flexible is this remember
几乎有些灵活，这是记住
the the folks that developed our socket
开发我们的套接字的人
knew about gr PC right at Facebook they
他们在Facebook上知道gr PC
they certainly understood what was
他们当然知道是什么
possible with that and they still chose
有可能，他们仍然选择
to develop their own to go their own way
发展自己的道路
because that was a better solution so my
因为那是一个更好的解决方案，所以我的
friends as I say thank you so much for
我说的朋友非常感谢你
watching I hope you got something out of
看着我希望你从中得到一些东西
this and we'll see you next time
这个，我们下次见
you
您